goole.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy - Goole

Please read this policy in conjunction with our [Cookies Policy](http://www.goole.com/cookies-policy/)

This Privacy Policy sets out how we, _Goole.com Limited_ , collect, store and use information about you when you use or interact with our website, _www.goole.com_ ] (our **website** ) and where we otherwise obtain or collect information about you. This Privacy Policy is effective from 24nd May 2018.

**Contents**

  * **Summary**
  * **Our details**
  * **Information we collect when you visit our website**
  * **Information we collect when you contact us**
  * **Our use of automated decision-making and profiling**
  * **How we collect or obtain information about you from third parties**
  * **Disclosure and additional uses of your information**
  * **How long we retain your information**
  * **How we secure your information**
  * **Transfers of your information outside the European Economic Area**
  * **Your rights in relation to your information**
  * **Your right to object to the processing of your information for certain purposes**
  * **Sensitive Personal Information**
  * **Changes to our Privacy Policy**
  * **Children’s Privacy**
  * **California Do Not Track Disclosures**
  * **Copyright, credit and logo**

**Summary**

This section summarises how we obtain, store and use information about you. It is intended to provide a very general overview only. **It is not complete in and of itself and it must be read in conjunction with the corresponding full sections of this Privacy Policy.**

  * **Data controller** : John Smith

  * **How we collect or obtain information about you** : 
    * when you provide it to us (e.g. by contacting us.),
    * from your use of our website, using cookies, and
    * occasionally, from third parties.
    * From existing internet websites.

  * **Information we collect** : Business or Organisation name, Address, Contact details, type of business, IP Address, information from cookies, information about your computer or device (e.g. device and browser type), information about how you use our website (e.g. which pages you have viewed, the time when you view them and what you clicked on, the geographical location from which you accessed our website (based on your IP address),
  * **How we use your information** : for administrative and business purposes, to improve our business and website, to analyse your use of our website, and in connection with our legal rights and obligations and To create directory listings with details of local businesses and organisations[2]

  * **Disclosure of your information to third parties** : only to the extent necessary to run our business, where required by law or to enforce our legal rights and We use data about individuals, businesses and organisations to display information to our website users. This information is sourced from existing websites and or supplied directly by you.

  * **Do we sell your information to third parties (other than in the course of a business sale or purchase or similar event)** : No

  * **How long we retain your information** : for no longer than necessary, taking into account any legal obligations we have e.g. to maintain records for tax purposes, any other legal basis we have for using your information e.g. your consent, performance of a contract with you or our legitimate interests as a business. For specific retention periods in relation to certain information which we collect from you, please see the main section below entitled _How long we retain your information_.

  * **How we secure your information** : using appropriate technical and organisational measures such as storing your information on secure servers, encrypting transfers of data to or from our servers using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology

  * **Use of cookies** : we do not use first party cookies on our website but there are third party cookies used – click here see our Cookies Policy

  * **Transfers of your information outside the European Economic Area** : We do not transfer your information.
  * **Use of automated decision making and profiling** : we do not use automated decision making and/or profiling but this may be used by our third party business partners – see our Cookie Policy.

  * **Your rights in relation to your information**
    * to access your information and to receive information about its use
    * to have your information corrected and/or completed
    * to have your information deleted
    * to restrict the use of your information
    * to receive your information in a portable format
    * to object to the use of your information
    * to withdraw your consent to the use of your information
    * not to have significant decisions made about you based solely on automated processing of your information, including profiling
    * to complain to a supervisory authority

  * **Sensitive personal information** : we do not knowingly or intentionally collect what is commonly referred to as ‘sensitive personal information’. Please do not submit sensitive personal information about you to us. For more information, please see the main section below entitled _Sensitive Personal Information_.

**Our details**

The data controller in respect of our website is Goole.com Limited company registration number: 04722419 of Stone Cross Rigg, Walton, Brampton, Cumbria CA8 2BA. You can contact the data controller by writing to Goole.com Limited, Stone Cross Rigg, Walton, Brampton, Cumbria CA8 2BA] or sending an email to info@goole.com.

The data controller’s representative is John Smith. You can contact the data controller’s representative by writing to John Smith, Goole.com Limited, Stone Cross Rigg, Walton, Brampton, Cumbria CA8 2BA or sending an email to info@goole.com.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact the data controller.

**Information we collect when you visit our website**

We collect and use information from website visitors in accordance with this section and the section entitled _Disclosure and additional uses of your information_.

**Web server log information**

We use a third party server to host our website called 1and1 Internet, the privacy policy of which is available here: https://www.1and1.co.uk/terms-gtc/terms-privacy/?linkId=nav.foot.account.privacy. Our website server automatically logs the IP address you use to access our website as well as other information about your visit such as [the pages accessed, information requested, the date and time of the request, the source of your access to our website (e.g. the website or URL (link) which referred you to our website), and your browser version and operating system.

Our server is located in Germany which is inside European Economic Area.

_Use of website server log information for IT security purposes_

We do not access log data from our website server. Our third party hosting provider collect(s) and store(s) server logs to ensure network and IT security and so that the server and website remain uncompromised. This includes analysing log files to help identify and prevent unauthorised access to our network, the distribution of malicious code, denial of services attacks and other cyber attacks, by detecting unusual or suspicious activity. Our hosting provider uses log data to allow us, on their website, to see analytical data.

Unless we are investigating suspicious or potential criminal activity, we do not make, nor do we allow our hosting provider to make, any attempt to identify you from the information collected via server logs.

**Legal basis for processing** : compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject (Article 6(1)(c) of the General Data Protection Regulation).  
**Legal obligation** : we have a legal obligation to implement appropriate technical and organisational measures to ensure a level of security appropriate to the risk of our processing of information about individuals. Recording access to our website using server log files is such a measure.

**Legal basis for processing** : our and a third party’s legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation).  
**Legitimate interests** : we and our third party hosting provider have a legitimate interest in using your information for the purposes of ensuring network and information security.

_Use of website server log information to analyse website use and improve our website_

We use the information collected by our website server logs to analyse how our website users interact with our website and its features. For example, we analyse the number of visits and unique visitors we receive, the time and date of the visit, the location of the visit and the operating system and browser used.

We use the information gathered from the analysis of this information to improve our website. For example, we use the information gathered to change the information, content and structure of our website and individual pages based according to what users are engaging most with and the duration of time spent on particular pages on our website.

**Legal basis for processing** : our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation).  
**Legitimate interest** : improving our website for our website users and getting to know our website users’ preferences so our website can better meet their needs and desires.

**Cookies**

Cookies are data files which are sent from a website to a browser to record information about users for various purposes.

We may use first party cookies on Goole.com and our third party partners do use cookies. on our website, including essential, functional, analytical and targeting. For further information on how we use cookies, please see our cookies policy which is available here: <http://www.goole.com/cookies-policy/> .

You can reject some or all of the cookies we use on or via our website by changing your browser settings but doing so can impair your ability to use our website or some or all of its features. For further information about cookies, including how to change your browser settings, please visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) or see our cookies policy.

**Information we collect when you contact us**

We collect and use information from individuals who contact us in accordance with this section and the section entitled _Disclosure and additional uses of your information_.

**Email**

When you send an email to the email address displayed on our website we collect your email address and any other information you provide in that email (such as your name, telephone number and the information contained in any signature block in your email).

**Legal basis for processing** : our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation).  
**Legitimate interest(s)** : responding to enquiries and messages we receive and keeping records of correspondence.

**Legal basis for processing** : necessary to perform a contract or to take steps at your request to enter into a contract (Article 6(1)(b) of the General Data Protection Regulation).  
**Reason why necessary to perform a contract** : where your message relates to us providing you with goods or services or taking steps at your request prior to providing you with our goods and services (for example, providing you with information about such goods and services), we will process your information in order to do so).

_Transfer and storage of your information_

We use a third party email provider to store emails you send us. Our third party email providers are BT Internet located in the UK and1and1 Internet based in Germany. Their privacy policies are available here: <https://www.productsandservices.bt.com/privacy-policy/> and <https://www.1and1.co.uk/terms-gtc/terms-privacy/?linkId=nav.foot.account.privacy> .

Emails you send us will be stored on our third party email provider’s servers in the UK and wider EU, India and the Philippines. For further information please see the section of this privacy policy entitled _Transfers of your information outside the European Economic Area_.

**Contact form**

At present, Goole.com does not use any contact forms

**Phone**

When you contact us by phone, we collect your phone number and any information provide to us during your conversation with us.

We do not record phone calls.

**Legal basis for processing** : our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation)  
**Legitimate interest(s)** : responding to enquiries and messages we receive and keeping records of correspondence.

**Legal basis for processing** : necessary to perform a contract or to take steps at your request to enter into a contract (Article 6(1)(b) of the General Data Protection Regulation).  
**Reason why necessary to perform a contract** : where your message relates to us providing you with goods or services or taking steps at your request prior to providing you with our goods and services (for example, providing you with information about such goods and services), we will process your information in order to do so).

_Transfer and storage of your information_

Information about your call, such as your phone number and the date and time of your call, is processed by our third party telephone service provider BT which is located in the UK and wider EU, India and the Philippines. Their privacy policy is available here: <https://www.productsandservices.bt.com/privacy-policy/>.

Information about your phone call will be stored by our third party telephone service provider with the UK and wider EU, India and the Philippines. For further information about the safeguards used when your information is transferred outside the European Economic Area, see the section of this privacy policy below entitled _Transfers of your information outside the European Economic Area_.

**Post**

If you contact us by post, we will collect any information you provide to us in any postal communications you send us.

**Legal basis for processing** : our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation)  
**Legitimate interest(s)** : responding to enquiries and messages we receive and keeping records of correspondence.

**Legal basis for processing** : necessary to perform a contract or to take steps at your request to enter into a contract (Article 6(1)(b) of the General Data Protection Regulation).  
**Reason why necessary to perform a contract** : where your message relates to us providing you with goods or services or taking steps at your request prior to providing you with our goods and services (for example, providing you with information about such goods and services), we will process your information in order to do so).

**Information we may collect when you interact with our website**

We collect and use information from individuals who interact with particular features of our website in accordance with this section and the section entitled _Disclosure and additional uses of your information_.

**E-Newsletter**

Goole.com does not produce or distribute an e-newsletter.

**Registering on our website**

Goole.com does not have any form of registering active on the website.

**Information we collect when you place an order on our website**

Goole.com does not sell goods or services on its website.

**Information collected or obtained from third parties**

This section sets out how we obtain or collect information about you from third parties.

**Information received from third parties**

Generally, we do not receive information about you from third parties.

**Where we receive information about you in error**

If we receive information about you from a third party in error and/or we do not have a legal basis for processing that information, we will delete your information.

**Information obtained by us from third parties**

In certain circumstances (for example, to verify the information we hold about you or obtain missing information we require to provide you with a service) we will obtain information about you from certain publicly accessible sources, both EU and non-EU, such as online customer databases, business directories, media publications, social media, and websites (including your own website if you have one.

Goole.com does not collect data from private sources.

**Legal basis for processing** : necessary to perform a contract or to take steps at your request to enter into a contract (Article 6(1)(b) of the General Data Protection Regulation).  
**Reason why necessary to perform a contract** : where you have entered into a contract or requested that we enter into a contract with you, in certain circumstances, we will obtain information about you from public sources in order to enable us to understand your business and provide services to you or services to a sufficient standard.

For example, we would obtain and/or verify your email address from your website or from a directory where you ask us to send you information by email but we do not possess the information or we need to confirm that we have recorded your email address correctly.

**Legal basis for processing** : our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation).  
**Legitimate interests** : in certain circumstances, we will have a legitimate interest in obtaining information about you from public and private sources. For example, if you have infringed or we suspect that you have infringed any of our legal rights, we will have a legitimate interest in obtaining and processing information about you from such sources in order to investigate and pursue any suspected or potential infringement.

**Our use of automated decision-making and profiling**

We do not use automated decision making and profiling on our website but our third party partners may do. See our cookies policy for details: http://www.goole.com/cookies-policy/. We do not consider that this has any legal effect on you or similarly significantly affects you.

You have the right to object to our use of automated decision making and profiling described in this section. You can do that by opting-out of cookies and similar technologies in accordance with the method described in the relevant section below. If you do not want us to process your actual IP address (usually the IP address assigned to you by your Internet Service Provider) when you visit our website, you can use a Virtual Private Network (VPN) or a free service such as Tor.

You can find out more about our use of cookies and similar technologies (including the legal basis on which we use them) and how to opt out from them in our cookies policy, which is available here: http://www.goole.com/cookies-policy/

**Automated decision making**

Automated decision making is decision making by technological means (i.e. by a machine) without human involvement.

_Use of automated decision making for display advertising_

We do not automate the display advertisements containing our products and services on other websites you visit, you based on the fact that you have visited our website using cookies. Our partners may use these methods. For further information on the cookies we use, please see our cookies policy which is available here: http://www.goole.com/cookies-policy/

**Profiling**

Profiling is any form of automated processing of your information to evaluate personal aspects about you, in particular to analyse or predict things like your performance at work, economic situation, health, personal preferences, interests, reliability, behaviour, location or movements.

Goole.com does not use profiling. Our partners may use these – see our cookies policy[ http://www.goole.com/cookies-policy/](http://www.goole.com/cookies-policy/)

**Disclosure and additional uses of your information**

This section sets out the circumstances in which will disclose information about you to third parties and any additional purposes for which we use your information.

**Disclosure of your information to service providers**

We use a number of third parties to provide us with services which are necessary to run our business or to assist us with running our business and who process your information for us on our behalf. These include the following:

  * Telephone provider is BT located in the UK. Their privacy policy is available here: <https://www.productsandservices.bt.com/privacy-policy/> .
  * Email provider are BT, located in the UK, and 1and1 Internet based in Germany. Their privacy policy is available here: <https://www.productsandservices.bt.com/privacy-policy/> and <https://www.1and1.co.uk/terms-gtc/terms-privacy/?linkId=nav.foot.account.privacy> .
  * IT service provider is 1and1 Internet based in Germany.Their privacy policy is available here :<https://www.1and1.co.uk/terms-gtc/terms-privacy/?linkId=nav.foot.account.privacy>
  * Hosting provider(s), see 1and1 Internet above.

Your information will be shared with these service providers where necessary to provide you with the service you have requested, whether that is accessing our website or ordering goods and services from us.

**Legal basis for processing** : legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation).  
**Legitimate interest relied on** : where we share your information with these third parties in a context other than where is necessary to perform a contract (or take steps at your request to do so), we will share your information with such third parties in order to allow us to run and manage our business efficiently.

**Legal basis for processing** : necessary to perform a contract and/or to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract (Article 6(1)(b) of the General Data Protection Regulation).  
**Reason why necessary to perform a contract** : we may need to share information with our service providers to enable us to perform our obligations under that contract or to take the steps you have requested before we enter into a contract with you.

**Disclosure of your information to other third parties**

We disclose your information to other third parties in specific circumstances, as set out below.

_Providing information to third parties such as _Google Inc._ _. Google collects information through our use of Google Analytics on our website. Google uses this information, including IP addresses and information from cookies, for a number of purposes, such as improving its Google Analytics service. Information is shared with Google on an aggregated and anonymised basis. To find out more about what information Google collects, how it uses this information and how to control the information sent to Google, please see the following page: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>

**Legal basis for processing** : our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation).

_Transfer and storage of your information_

Information collected by Google Analytics is stored outside the European Economic Area on Google’s servers in the United States of America.

For further information about the safeguards used when your information is transferred outside the European Economic Area, see the section of this privacy policy below entitled _Transfers of your information outside the European Economic Area_.]

_Sharing your information with third parties, which are either related to or associated with the running of our business, where it is necessary for us to do so. These third parties include our web developer._ Further information on each of these third parties is set out below.

**Legal basis for processing** : our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation).  
**Legitimate interest** : running and managing our business efficiently.

__Independent contractors__

We use independent contractors in our business. Your information will be shared with independent contractors only where it is necessary for them to perform the function we have hired them perform in relation to our business.

Our independent contractors are the web developer Rocket Sites . Their privacy policy is available here: [_https://www.rocketsites.co.uk/privacy-policy/_](https://www.rocketsites.co.uk/privacy-policy/). Our independent contractors are located in the UK.

**  Legal basis for processing**: our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation). **  
Legitimate interest** : running and managing our business effectively.

**AND/OR**

**Legal basis for processing** : necessary to perform a contract or to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract] (Article 6(1)(b) of the General Data Protection Regulation). **  
Reason why necessary to perform a contract** : we need to share your information with other companies in order to be able to meet our contractual obligations to you or to take steps at your request prior to entering a contract, for example because of the services or information you have requested.

We do not display the identities of all of the other third parties we may share information with by name for security and competitive reasons. If you would like further information about the identities of such third parties, however, please contact us  by email and we will provide you with such information where you have a legitimate reason for requesting it (where we have shared your information with such third parties, for example).

_Sharing your information with a prospective or actual purchaser or seller in the context of a business or asset sale or acquisition by us, a merger or similar business combination event, whether actual or potential._

**Legal basis for processing** : legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation). **  
Legitimate interest(s)** : sharing your information with a prospective purchaser, seller or similar person in order to allow such a transaction to take place.

**Disclosure and use of your information for legal reasons**

_Indicating possible criminal acts or threats to public security to a competent authority_

If we suspect that criminal or potential criminal conduct has been occurred, we will in certain circumstances need to contact an appropriate authority, such as the police. This could be the case, for instance, if we suspect that we fraud or a cybercrime has been committed or if we receive threats or malicious communications towards us or third parties.

We will generally only need to process your information for this purpose if you were involved or affected by such an incident in some way.

**Legal basis for processing** : our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation).  
**Legitimate interests** : preventing crime or suspected criminal activity (such as fraud).

_In connection with the enforcement or potential enforcement our legal rights_

We will use your information in connection with the enforcement or potential enforcement of our legal rights, including, for example, sharing information with debt collection agencies if you do not pay amounts owed to us when you are contractually obliged to do so. Our legal rights may be contractual (where we have entered into a contract with you) or non-contractual (such as legal rights that we have under copyright law or tort law).

**Legal basis for processing** : our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation).  
**Legitimate interest:** enforcing our legal rights and taking steps to enforce our legal rights.

_In connection with a legal or potential legal dispute or proceedings_

We may need to use your information if we are involved in a dispute with you or a third party for example, either to resolve the dispute or as part of any mediation, arbitration or court resolution or similar process.

**Legal basis for processing:** our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation).  
**Legitimate interest(s):** resolving disputes and potential disputes.

_For ongoing compliance with laws, regulations and other legal requirements_

We will use and process your information in order to comply with legal obligations to which we are subject. For example, we may need to disclose your information pursuant to a court order or subpoena if we receive one or to the National Crime Agency in connection with suspected or potential money laundering matters.

**Legal basis for processing** : compliance with a legal obligation (Article 6(1)(c) of the General Data Protection Regulation). **  
Legal obligation(s)** : legal obligations to disclose information which are part of the laws of England and Wales or if they have been integrated into the United Kingdom’s legal framework (for example in the form of an international agreement which the United Kingdom has signed).

**Legal basis for processing** : our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation).  
**Legitimate interest** : where the legal obligations are part of the laws of another country and have not been integrated into the United Kingdom’s legal framework, we have a legitimate interest in complying with these obligations.

**How long we retain your information**

This section sets out how long we retain your information. We have set out specific retention periods where possible. Where that has not been possible, we have set out the criteria we use to determine the retention period.

**Retention periods**

_Server log information_ : we retain information on our server logs indefinitely to allow us to monitor performance from each year.

_Correspondence and enquiries_ : when you make an enquiry or correspond with us for any reason, whether by email or by phone, we will retain your information for as long as it takes to respond to and resolve your enquiry, and for a further 3 months after which point we will delete your information unless the information may be required in the future for dispute resolution between our business and the data subject.

**Criteria for determining retention periods**

In any other circumstances, we will retain your information for no longer than necessary, taking into account the following:

  * the purpose(s) and use of your information both now and in the future (such as whether it is necessary to continue to store that information in order to continue to perform our obligations under a contract with you or to contact you in the future);
  * whether we have any legal obligation to continue to process your information (such as any record-keeping obligations imposed by relevant law or regulation);
  * whether we have any legal basis to continue to process your information (such as your consent);
  * how valuable your information is (both now and in the future);
  * any relevant agreed industry practices on how long information should be retained;
  * the levels of risk, cost and liability involved with us continuing to hold the information;
  * how hard it is to ensure that the information can be kept up to date and accurate; and
  * any relevant surrounding circumstances (such as the nature and status of our relationship with you).

**How we secure your information**

We take appropriate technical and organisational measures to secure your information and to protect it against unauthorised or unlawful use and accidental loss or destruction, including:

  * only sharing and providing access to your information to the minimum extent necessary, subject to confidentiality restrictions where appropriate, and on an anonymised basis wherever possible;
  * using secure servers to store your information
  * verifying the identity of any individual who requests access to information prior to granting them access to information;
  * only transferring your information via closed system or encrypted data transfers;
  * Physical security systems to prevent access to physical files and equipment.

**Transmission of information to us by email**

Transmission of information over the internet is not entirely secure, and if you submit any information to us over the internet (whether by email or any other means), you do so entirely at your own risk.

We cannot be responsible for any costs, expenses, loss of profits, harm to reputation, damages, liabilities or any other form of loss or damage suffered by you as a result of your decision to transmit information to us by such means.

**Transfers of your information outside the European Economic Area**

All of your information is stored in the following European Economic Area (EEA) countries : Germany and the UK. Information is also stored by Google in the USA and BT in India, and the Philippines.

Other than to comply with any legal obligations to which we are subject (compliance with a court order, for example), we do not intend to transfer your information outside the EEA or to an international organisation (other than those detailed above). In the unlikely event that we are required to transfer your information outside the EEA (or to an international organisation) for such a purpose, we will ensure appropriate safeguards and protections are in place.

**_Server log information_**

Information collected when you visit our website is not transferred outside of the EEA and stored on the servers of our third party hosting company, _1and1 Internet – see details above_.

**_Email_**

Information collected when you e-mail us is not transferred outside of the EEA and stored on the servers of our third party hosting company[, _1and1 Internet – see details above_.

**_Google Analytics_**

Information collected by Google Analytics (your IP address and actions you take in relation to our website) is transferred outside the EEA and stored on Google’s servers. You can access Google’s privacy policy here: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>

_Country of storage_ : United States of America. This country is not subject to an adequacy decision by the European Commission.

_Safeguard(s) used_ : Google has self-certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield which is available here: <https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome>. The EU-U.S. Privacy Shield is an approved certification mechanism under Article 42 of the General Data Protection Regulation, which is permitted under Article 46(2)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation. You can access the European Commission decision on the adequacy of the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield here: <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/international-transfers/adequacy/index_en.htm>

**Your rights in relation to your information**

Subject to certain limitations on certain rights, you have the following rights in relation to your information, which you can exercise by writing to Goole.com Limited, Stonecross Rigg, Walton, Brampton, Cumbria, CA8 2BA or sending an email to info@goole.com.

  * **to request access to your information** and information related to our use and processing of your information;
  * **to request the correction or deletion** of your information;
  * **to request that we restrict our use** of your information;
  * **to receive information which you have provided to us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format** (e.g. a CSV file) and the right to have that information transferred to another data controller (including a third party data controller);
  * **to object to the processing of your information for certain purposes** (for further information, see the section below entitled _Your right to object to the processing of your information for certain purposes_ ); and
  * **to withdraw your consent to our use of your information** at any time where we rely on your consent to use or process that information. Please note that if you withdraw your consent, this will not affect the lawfulness of our use and processing of your information on the basis of your consent before the point in time when you withdraw your consent.
  * **the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling which produces legal affects concerning you or similarly significantly affects you**

In accordance with Article 77 of the General Data Protection Regulation, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the Member State of your habitual residence, place of work or of an alleged infringement of the General Data Protection Regulation.

For the purposes of the UK, the supervisory authority is the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), the contact details of which are available here: <https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/>

_Further information on your rights in relation to your personal data as an individual_

The above rights are provided in summary form only and certain limitations apply to many of these rights. For further information about your rights in relation to your information, including any limitations which apply, please visit the following pages on the ICO’s website:

  * <https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/>; and
  * <https://ico.org.uk/for-the-public/is-my-information-being-handled-correctly/>

You can also find out further information about your rights, as well as information on any limitations which apply to those rights, by reading the underlying legislation contained in Articles 12 to 22 and 34 of the General Data Protection Regulation, which is available here: <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/reform/files/regulation_oj_en.pdf>

_Verifying your identity where you request access to your information_

Where you request access to your information, we are required by law to use all reasonable measures to verify your identity before doing so.

These measures are designed to protect your information and to reduce the risk of identity fraud, identity theft or general unauthorised access to your information.

_How we verify your identity_

Where we possess appropriate information about you on file, we will attempt to verify your identity using that information.

If it is not possible to identity you from such information, or if we have insufficient information about you, we may require original or certified copies of certain documentation in order to be able to verify your identity before we are able to provide you with access to your information.

We will be able to confirm the precise information we require to verify your identity in your specific circumstances if and when you make such a request.

**Your right to object to the processing of your information for certain purposes**

You have the following rights in relation to your information, which you may exercise in the same way as you may exercise by writing to Goole.com Limited, Stonecross Rigg, Walton, Brampton, Cumbria, CA8 2BA or sending an email to info@goole.com.

  * to object to us using or processing your information where we use or process it in order to **carry out a task in the public interest** **or for our legitimate interests** , including ‘profiling’ (i.e. analysing or predicting your behaviour based on your information) based on any of these purposes; and
  * to object to us using or processing your information for **direct marketing purposes** (including any profiling we engage in that is related to such direct marketing).

For more information on how to object to our use of information collected from cookies and similar technologies, please see the section entitled _How to accept or reject cookies_ in our cookies policy, which is available here: <http://www.goole.com/cookies-policy/> .

**Sensitive Personal Information**

‘Sensitive personal information’ is information about an individual that reveals their racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership, genetic information, biometric information for the purpose of uniquely identifying an individual, information concerning health or information concerning a natural person’s sex life or sexual orientation.

We do not knowingly or intentionally collect sensitive personal information from individuals, and you must not submit sensitive personal information to us.

If, however, you inadvertently or intentionally transmit sensitive personal information to us, you will be considered to have explicitly consented to us processing that sensitive personal information under Article 9(2)(a) of the General Data Protection Regulation. We will use and process your sensitive personal information for the purposes of deleting it.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We update and amend our Privacy Policy from time to time.

_Minor changes to our Privacy Policy_

Where we make minor changes to our Privacy Policy, we will update our Privacy Policy with a new effective date stated at the beginning of it. Our processing of your information will be governed by the practices set out in that new version of the Privacy Policy from its effective date onwards.

_Major changes to our Privacy Policy or the purposes for which we process your information_

Where we make major changes to our Privacy Policy or intend to use your information for a new purpose or a different purpose than the purposes for which we originally collected it, we will notify you by email (where possible) or by posting a notice on our website.

We will provide you with the information about the change in question and the purpose and any other relevant information before we use your information for that new purpose.

Wherever required, we will obtain your prior consent before using your information for a purpose that is different from the purposes for which we originally collected it.

**Children’s Privacy**

Because we care about the safety and privacy of children online, we comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). COPPA and its accompanying regulations protect the privacy of children using the internet. We do not knowingly contact or collect information from persons under the age of 18. The website is not intended to solicit information of any kind from persons under the age of 18.

It is possible that we could receive information pertaining to persons under the age of 18 by the fraud or deception of a third party. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will, where required by law to do so, immediately obtain the appropriate parental consent to use that information or, if we are unable to obtain such parental consent, we will delete the information from our servers. If you would like to notify us of our receipt of information about persons under the age of 18, please do so by writing to Goole.com Limited, Stonecross Rigg, Walton, Brampton, Cumbria, CA8 2BA or sending an email to info@goole.com.

**Copyright, credit and logo**

This Privacy Policy is based on a General Data Protection Regulation (Regulation (EU) 2016/769) (GDPR) compliant template provided by GDPR Privacy Policy. For further information, please visit [https://gdprprivacypolicy.org](https://gdprprivacypolicy.org/)

The copyright in this Privacy Policy is either owned by, or licensed to, us and is protected by copyright laws around the world and copyright protection software. All intellectual property rights in this document are reserved.

Where we display the GDPR Privacy Policy logo on our website, this is used to indicate that we have adopted a privacy policy template provided by GDPR Privacy Policy as the basis for this Privacy Policy.
